RESUME

Monday, 29-05-2021



EDUCATION

OCT 2006 - APR 2012

Bachelor's degree

Faculty of Computer and Information Science, Ljubljana

SKILLS

HTML / CSS

React.js

Vue.js

Node.js

TDD / BDD

Other Skills: ES6, Docker, mocha, chai, bootstrap, jQuery, webpack, gulp, sass, Jenkins, AWS CodeDeploy, git, github, backbone.js, angular.js.

MIHA ERZEN

TECH LEAD SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Phone: +49 | 157 5300 | 1741 | Email: miha.erzen | @gmail.com | Web: miha.website

Linkedin: linkedin.com/in/miha-erzen

ABOUT ME

I'm a 33 years old tech lead software engineer currently based in Berlin. I love everything that has to do with software development, architectural planning and mentoring peers. Building products with great UX is something I'm really passionate about.

WORK EXPERIENCE

JAN 2020 - Current

Senior Software Engineer

Boxplot, Berlin - DE

Building B2B applications tailored to the needs of our clients. We specialize in data mining with a focus on customer activities. My daily responsibilities consist of planning, defining and improving our architecture, writing code, reviewing pull requests and mentoring peers. Majority of my development time I spend writing React.js and Node.js code.

JAN 2019 - DEC 2020

Senior Software Engineer, Freelance

Skill Yoga, Berlin - DE

I was in charge of building the react native yoga app with React.js, Redux on top of AWS serverless API and Firebase. App is available on the app store and has currently a rating of 4.7.

FEB 2014 - DEC 2018

Tech lead, Senior software engineer

Fanmiles, Berlin - DE

Making sure the product vision was aligned with the architectural and infrastructural vision of the platform, I acted as an architect a team lead and an engineering manager with a hands-on approach.

REFERENCES

MR. JENS DRESSLER

Founder & CEO @ GraphApi.io

E: jens@anywhereinside.com

P: +49 163 6282977

MR. LUIS DANIEL ALEGRIA

Head of Product for E-Commerce (LATAM)

E: alegria@cvccorp.com.br **P:** +55 (11) 99570-4384